http://www.saf.com/about-us/privacy-statement/

Stock 5005 AQ sheet
Why 5005 Aluminum Sheet ?
Metal Wall Panels
SAF’s 3-Day Out!!!
Current Anodizing Processes
Custom Anodizing – What is it?
Anodizing FAQs
Light & Medium Bronze-EXPECT COLOR VARIATION!
SAF Privacy Statement
Southern Aluminum Finishing Co (“SAF“) regards the privacy and security of user information as a critical component of the products and services that we offer on our web site(s) (collectively, the “Site“). The following privacy statement (“Privacy Statement“) discloses our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information on the Site.
Information Collected
SAF may collect both Aggregate Information and Personally Identifiable Information on the Site. “Aggregate Information” is information that describes the habits and other behavioral traits of the users of the Site as a group but does not indicate the identity of a particular user. Generally, this information is collected through “traffic data” and may entail the use of “Cookies”, “IP addresses” or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. The use of “Cookies” on the site is explained in more detail below in the IP Address and Cookies section. “Personally Identifiable Information” refers to information you voluntarily provide to SAF that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, e-mail address, company name, address, or telephone number.
Use of Aggregate Information
SAF may use Aggregate Information to perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our registered users and visitors, to measure user behavior regarding specific areas of the Site and to analyze how and where best to use our resources. Without such data, we would not know which parts of the Site are the most popular, and we would not be able to change and update the content and services appropriately. We may use Aggregate Information to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site, and for product monitoring and improvement. SAF also may use the Aggregate Information collected to let our partners know the number of people who have certain browser characteristics and the number of those people who have seen and/or “clicked” on individual advertisement(s). No Personally Identifiable Information will be disclosed to these partners as part of this process.
Use of Personally Identifiable Information
SAF does not collect Personally Identifiable Information about you except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis, as prompted by the Site in the circumstances described below.
(a)  Required Disclosure: SAF will only disclose Personally Identifiable Information without your permission if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served on SAF or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SAF; (c) enforce the SAF Terms of Sale; or (d) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public.
(b) E-Mail Promotions: If you choose to receive promotional e-mails from SAF, we will ask you to provide SAF with your e-mail address. If at any time after you subscribe to receive e-mail promotions, you may unsubscribe by replying to SAF with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject heading of your e-mail.
(c) Product and Service Purchases/Enquiries: We ask for Personally Identifiable Information when you purchase a product or service through SAF’s  Aluminum Store.  When you purchase a product or service, SAF will collect your credit card and shipping information for billing purposes. SAF does not store, use or share your credit card information for any other purpose.  SAF uses security techniques, including encryption and secure servers, to help protect against unauthorized access to transmitted information used for billing purposes.
SAF will collect Personally Identifiable Information from you when you request additional information about a particular product or service listed on the Site, so that a SAF sales representative or local partner is able to contact you to provide the information you have requested.
(e) Service/Support Related Correspondence: If you register to use a SAF product or otherwise purchase a product from this Site, SAF may use your e-mail contact information to deliver technical support-related service information, as applicable. We will not send you unrelated promotional e-mails unless you have specifically asked to receive them. If you register to use a SAF product or otherwise purchase a product from this Site, you will not be able to unsubscribe from receiving technical support-related service e-mails (unless your license rights expire or are terminated), as these e-mails are considered part of the service you have chosen.  SAF will, however, try to honor your requests to avoid service emails if you request it.
(f) Correspondence: If you contact SAF, we may keep a record of that correspondence. If you communicate with SAF via e-mail, we may keep a record of your e-mail address, but we will not disclose your e-mail address except as permitted under this Privacy Statement.
Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information
SAF feels strongly that your Personally Identifiable Information should only be seen by you, unless you choose to share it with others. We will never sell, rent, license or exchange Personally Identifiable Information to or with a third party without your permission, except as permitted under this Privacy Statement. SAF will only share your Personally Identifiable Information with our partners to the extent necessary to fulfill your orders for goods and services purchased on the Site. We will employ reasonable efforts to require these partners to abide by this Privacy Statement and not further use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose other than providing us or you with products and services.
Children
The SAF products and services offered on the Site are not available to children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has registered or is attempting to register with the Site, we will notify the user that he is not eligible to become a member. We will also expunge any Personally Identifiable Information from our records, barring that which is used to block the child from our service.
Security
Information collected by SAF is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. All of our employees are dedicated to maintaining and upholding your privacy and security and are aware of our privacy and security policies. Although we use industry-standard practices to protect your privacy, we cannot guarantee, and you should not expect, that your Personally Identifiable Information or private communications will remain private under all circumstances. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or stored information. We cannot and do not assume any responsibility or liability for any information you submit to us or your or a third party’s use or misuse of information transmitted or received during use of the Site. You are responsible for taking all reasonable steps to ensure that no unauthorized person shall have access to your SAF password, if you are assigned a password to access a product or restricted area of the Site. To the extent applicable, it is your sole responsibility to (1) control the dissemination and use of your password; (2) authorize, monitor, and control access to and use of this Site and any SAF product; (3) promptly inform SAF if you need to deactivate a password.
Other Web Sites and Links
This Site contains links to other web sites. SAF’s partners may also have links on this Site. The privacy practices of those partners or web sites linked to SAF are not covered by this Privacy Statement and SAF is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Additionally, if you make a purchase from a store or merchant listed on or linked to the Site, any information that you give, such as your credit card number and contact information, is provided to those merchants. These merchants have separate privacy and data collection practices and SAF has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies.
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy policies posted on each and every site you may visit.
IP Addresses and Cookies
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad statistical information. IP addresses are also used to provide an audit trail in the case of attempted illegal use of the Site as well as to guard against spamming. SAF may use “Cookies” – a Cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the Cookie to you. The purpose of a Cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific web page. Cookies allow us to know how often users visit the Site and the activities that users conduct while on the Site. This allows SAF to statistically monitor how many people are using the Site and for what purpose. You have the ability to accept or decline Cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline Cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline Cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site.
Updating, Editing, and Deleting Information
As a user of the Site, you may update or edit your account information that you have previously entered by sending an e-mail to SAF at sales@saf.com, detailing the account information that you wish to have updated or edited. SAF will change your account information accordingly, and confirm the changes by replying to your e-mail. You may also send an e-mail to SAF at sales@saf.com requesting that we delete your account information. To the extent permitted by applicable law, SAF will delete your account information, and confirm the deletion of your account information by replying to your e-mail. If you have registered to use a SAF product or otherwise have purchased a product from this Site, your account information may not be deleted by us until your license rights expire or are terminated.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
SAF will occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When SAF posts changes to this Privacy Statement, you will see the word “updated” next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of SAF. If there are material changes to this Privacy Statement or in how SAF will use your Personally Identifiable Information, SAF will prominently post such changes prior to implementing them. SAF encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to be informed of how SAF is protecting your information.
Your use of this Site constitutes your acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Statement, and your continued usage after any changes in this Privacy Statement are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement or any revised Privacy Statement, please exit this Site immediately.
1581 Huber Street Northwest, Atlanta, GA | toll free: +1-800-241-7429 | +1-404-355-1560
©2020 SAF Southern Aluminum Finishing Company. Inc. | www.saf.com | Privacy Statement
